oneload.com 2016-05-13

# Privacy Policy - Video Distribution Simplified : OneLoad - OneLoad

**TubeMogul Privacy & Security Policy**  
TubeMogul provides a platform that is designed to help advertisers place advertisements into videos that you view while online. Our video advertising platform integrates real-time media buying, ad serving, targeting, optimization and brand measurement to help our advertising clients simplify the delivery of video ads and maximizes the impact of those advertisements. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at comments@tubemogul.com TubeMogul is a member of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) and complies with the NAI’s Self-Regulatory Principles. 

 **Ad Targeting and Opt-out**  
TubeMogul offers a technology platform for online video advertising. The platform is designed to value and place bids on individual ad impressions across major inventory suppliers, exchanges, and direct sites. We provide video ad delivery and reporting for clients, and enable our clients to use data segments based on their own non-personally identifiable information (“Non-PII”) regarding you and other web users, and Non-PII data segments supplied by third-party data companies to help ensure that the ads delivered to you via our platform our relevant to your interests. We describe this process in more detail below under the section entitled “Information Collected and Used by the TubeMogul video advertising platform.” If you prefer not to receive targeted video ads via our platform as described above you can opt out by clicking the link below: 

Note that opting out will not prevent you from seeing video ads – it will only make video ads being served by TubeMogul’s video advertising platform less relevant to your interests. Also, if you opt out and later delete your cookies, use a different browser or buy a new computer, you will need to renew your opt-out choice. Additionally, you may [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to access the opt out page maintained by the NAI, which provides additional information and a mechanism to opt out of interest based advertising from some or all NAI member companies. 

 **Information Collected and Used by the TubeMogul Video Advertising Platform**  
TubeMogul’s platform collects Non-PII. Non-PII is information that cannot by itself be used to identify a particular person or entity. Our video advertising platform collects Non-PII about the website(s) that you visit and the ads that you see online. The information collected may include your IP host address, pages viewed, browser type, Internet browsing and usage habits, Internet Service Provider, domain name, the time/date of your visit to a website where our platform is delivering ads, whether you have responded to one of our clients’ ads, the referring URL and your computer’s operating system. We provide the Non-PII data collected by our platform to our clients, who generally consider it to be their data. We also enable our advertising clients to integrate Non-PII data segments purchased from third-party data companies onto the platform in order to increase the relevance of those ads. We don’t place personally identifiable information such as your name, email address or telephone number (“PII”) onto the video advertising platform and we don’t allow our clients to do so. Similarly, we don’t place data segments that we consider to be sensitive onto the platform and don’t allow our clients to do so. Data that we consider to be “sensitive” includes social security numbers or other government-issued identifiers, insurance plan numbers, financial account numbers, precise information about past, present, or potential future health or medical conditions or treatments, including genetic, genomic, and family medical history, and sexual orientation. And while flash is sometimes used to enable the delivery of online video, the platform does not use flash, flash cookies or HTML5 persistent storage for any reason. We and our clients sometimes use health related targeting data segments provided by third party data companies, however these segments do not contain sensitive data (as described above). The non-sensitive health related data segments that can be used on our platform are in the following categories: (1) occupation in a health related field, (2) health related topics and conditions (but not specific conditions), (3) health insurance, (4) diet, fitness, weight-loss and healthy lifestyles, (5) consumer goods and services for personal healthcare, visioncare, grooming and beauty, (5) over the counter medicines, remedies and dietary supplements, and (6) health related charities. Overall the TubeMogul video advertising platform allows our clients to use the information collected and Non-PII data segments supplied by our clients and other third parties in order to help make the online ads you see more relevant to you, and the platform also uses collected information in aggregate for ad delivery and reporting purposes. If you prefer not to see targeted ads via the platform, you may opt-out by clicking [here](http://www.oneload.com/public/set_opt_out_cookie). Note that opting out will not prevent you from seeing video ads – it will only make video ads being served by TubeMogul’s platform less relevant to your interests. Also, if you opt out and later delete your cookies, use a different browser or buy a new computer, you will need to renew your opt-out choice. 

 **Cookies**  
“Cookies” are small files placed on the hard drive of your computer. TubeMogul’s video advertising platform uses cookies to help us understand and analyze how our clients cookies are employed to track stream and viewership data and to improve user experience by providing information such as buffering events per user back to our video site partners. We also use the data collected to report on effectiveness of campaigns for our clients and to optimize campaigns as they run to improve viewing time and brand awareness metrics. We also use web beacons on the platform to help use utilize third party data partners in order to make the ads we deliver more relevant. For more information about cookies and web beacons, please visit www.allaboutcookies.org. 

 **Data Collection and Use on TubeMogul.com**  
TubeMogul.com is primarily directed to video advertisers, website publishers and other clients and business partners. We typically collect personally identifiable information such as name, email address and telephone number (“PII”) via TubeMogul.com when it is provided to us, and generally use it for the purpose in which it was provided to us. For example, if a video advertiser sends an email or fills out a request form asking for more information about our products and services, we typically respond with a call and/or email providing that additional information. We enable our clients with a user ID and password so they may view their accounts via TubeMogul. Please don’t give out or share your account password. If you forget your password go to the following webpage to be emailed a password reminder, [click here](https://www.oneload.com/forgot_password). In the event that you suspect that your account password has been or will be misused, please immediately inform TubeMogul. In no event shall TubeMogul be responsible for any misuse(s) of use accounts or passwords. 

 **Platform Data Retention and Storage**  
We retain the Non-PII collected via our video advertising platform for up to three years. When we store Non-PII in cookies to help target ads on behalf of clients, we set those cookies to expire 12months from the date and time our services recognized our cookie on your computer. All data is encrypted and stored on our servers in the United States. 

 **Information Relating to Children**  
TubeMogul’s products and services are designed for those 13 years of age and older. TubeMogul does not knowingly collect PII from anyone under the age of 13. If the company is made aware that it has received PII from someone under 13, it will use reasonable efforts to remove that information from its records. 

 **Security**  
We take reasonable security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include firewalls and encryption, internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems. All account information is encrypted and stored on our servers in the United States. No method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure; therefore, while the company strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, it cannot guarantee absolute security. If you have any questions about these security practices, please email comments@tubemogul.com. 

 **Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**  
TubeMogul may share Non-PII collected on TubeMogul.com or via our video advertising platform with unaffiliated third parties for our business purposes. We may also share user level Non-PII and aggregate Non-PII collected via our video advertising platform with unaffiliated third parties for our business purposes, including but not limited to enabling our business partners to help us target ads via the video advertising platform. This information cannot be used to contact or identify any person individually. TubeMogul may also disclose your information to third parties when obligated to do so by law and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected, or actual prohibited activities, including but not limited to fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person. Finally, TubeMogul may transfer any information we possess, including any PII collected via TubeMogul.com, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets, bankruptcy, or other corporate change. If TubeMogul is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your PII, as well as any choices you may have regarding your PII. 

 **Your Consent**  
By using this site, you signify your assent to the TubeMogul Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to make changes in this policy at any time. Please check this policy frequently to ensure you are aware of any changes in our privacy practices. Our Privacy Policy will indicate the date it was last updated. Your continued use of our site will signify your acceptance of the changes to our Privacy Policy. 

 **Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
This privacy policy is subject to change. If the company plans to make any material changes in the way it uses the PII collected via TubeMogul.com, it will post a clear and conspicuous notice on TubeMogul.com and/or on this privacy policy prior to the changes being made. 

 **Contact Us**  
Please contact us to report violations or if you have any questions regarding our Privacy & Security policy. You can reach us at [comments@oneload.com](mailto:comments@oneload.com). Last updated on December 27, 2013.
